https://packardprovinggrounds.org/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
Protecting your private information is our priority. This Statement of Privacy applies to packardprovinggrounds.org and Packard Proving Motor Car Foundation and governs data collection and usage. For the purposes of this Privacy Policy, unless otherwise noted, all references to Packard Proving Motor Car Foundation include packardprovinggrounds.org, packardprovinggrounds.com, packardweddings.com, packardweddings.org, shelbyfarmersmarket.com, shelbyfarmersmarket.org, packardevents.com, packardevents.org, packardmotorfdn.com, and packardmotorfdn.org. The Packard Proving Grounds website is a news / information and ecommerce site. By using the Packard Proving Grounds website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.
Collection of your Personal Information
In order to better provide you with products and services offered on our Site, Packard Proving Grounds may collect personally identifiable information, such as your:
– First and Last Name
– Mailing Address
– E-mail Address
– Phone Number
If you purchase Packard Proving Grounds’s products and services, we collect billing and credit card information. This information is used to complete the purchase transaction.
Packard Proving Grounds may also collect anonymous demographic information, which is not unique to you, such as your:
– Age
– Gender
– geographical location
We do not collect any personal information about you unless you voluntarily provide it to us. However, you may be required to provide certain personal information to us when you elect to use certain products or services available on the Site. These may include: (a) registering for an account on our Site; (b) entering a sweepstakes or contest sponsored by us or one of our partners; (c) signing up for special offers from selected third parties; (d) sending us an email message; (e) submitting your credit card or other payment information when ordering and purchasing products and services on our Site. To wit, we will use your information for, but not limited to, communicating with you in relation to services and/or products you have requested from us. We also may gather additional personal or non-personal information in the future.
Use of your Personal Information
Packard Proving Grounds collects and uses your personal information to operate its website(s) and deliver the services you have requested.
Packard Proving Grounds may also use your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from Packard Proving Grounds and its affiliates.
Sharing Information with Third Parties
Packard Proving Grounds does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties.
Packard Proving Grounds may share data with trusted partners to help perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to Packard Proving Grounds, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.
Packard Proving Grounds may disclose your personal information, without notice, if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on Packard Proving Grounds or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Packard Proving Grounds; and/or (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of Packard Proving Grounds, or the public.
Tracking User Behavior
Packard Proving Grounds may keep track of the websites and pages our users visit within Packard Proving Grounds, in order to determine what Packard Proving Grounds services are the most popular. This data is used to deliver customized content and advertising within Packard Proving Grounds to customers whose behavior indicates that they are interested in a particular subject area.
Automatically Collected Information
Information about your computer hardware and software may be automatically collected by Packard Proving Grounds. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring website addresses. This information is used for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the Packard Proving Grounds website.
Links
This website contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of any other site that collects personally identifiable information.
Security of your Personal Information
Packard Proving Grounds secures your personal information from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure. Packard Proving Grounds uses the following methods for this purpose:
– SSL Protocol
When personal information (such as a credit card number) is transmitted to other websites, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) protocol.
We strive to take appropriate security measures to protect against unauthorized access to or alteration of your personal information. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet or any wireless network can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your personal information, you acknowledge that: (a) there are security and privacy limitations inherent to the Internet which are beyond our control; and (b) security, integrity, and privacy of any and all information and data exchanged between you and us through this Site cannot be guaranteed.
Children Under Thirteen
Packard Proving Grounds does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of thirteen. If you are under the age of thirteen, you must ask your parent or guardian for permission to use this website.
E-mail Communications
From time to time, Packard Proving Grounds may contact you via email for the purpose of providing announcements, promotional offers, alerts, confirmations, surveys, and/or other general communication.
If you would like to stop receiving marketing or promotional communications via email from Packard Proving Grounds, you may opt out of such communications by replying STOP or clicking on the UNSUBSCRIBE button.
External Data Storage Sites
We may store your data on servers provided by third party hosting vendors with whom we have contracted.
Changes to this Statement
Packard Proving Grounds reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your account, by placing a prominent notice on our site, and/or by updating any privacy information on this page. Your continued use of the Site and/or Services available through this Site after such modifications will constitute your: (a) acknowledgment of the modified Privacy Policy; and (b) agreement to abide and be bound by that Policy.
Contact Information
Packard Proving Grounds welcomes your questions or comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that Packard Proving Grounds has not adhered to this Statement, please contact Packard Proving Grounds at:
Packard Proving Motor Car Foundation
49965 Van Dyke Ave
Shelby Township, Michigan 48317
Email Address:
maryanne@packardprovinggrounds.org
Telephone number:
586-739-4800
Effective as of January 01, 2019
The Packard Proving Grounds Historic Site is owned by The Packard Motor Car Foundation & is a non-profit 501(c)(3) organization. It is funded by foundation grants, individual & corporate contributions, service groups & events. All donations to The Packard Motor Car Foundation are tax-deductible to the full extent permitted by law.
Proud Member Of:Where to Find Us Packard Proving Grounds
49965 Van Dyke Ave
Shelby Township, MI 48317
(586) 739-4800 – Site
Info email
Hours: 9am -3pm every day
Check ahead, sometimes closed for tours during private events (on the weekends especially).
Curious about weddings held on the PPG grounds? PackardWeddings.org
Check out the farmers market that’s held on the front lawn of the PPG, May through October, on Saturdays 9 am – 2pm ShelbyFarmersMarket.org
Scroll to top
